<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ens on Caroline Sorin</title>
    <link>http://carolinesorin.com/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ens on Caroline Sorin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:32:46 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://carolinesorin.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Not in my Backyard</title>
      <link>http://carolinesorin.com/en/backyard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:32:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://carolinesorin.com/en/backyard/</guid>
      <description>Not in my Backyard In 2013, an abandoned train station in a wealthy neighborhood of Paris is about to be replaced by a block of council flats despite the loud opposition of its neighbors. A few weeks before the works begin, I went there to immortalize this urban wasteland, symbol of the class war in the 16th arrondissement.
20 x 28 cm, 16 pages, digital print, saddle stitch binding, 2013</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mash Up</title>
      <link>http://carolinesorin.com/en/archi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://carolinesorin.com/en/archi/</guid>
      <description> Mash up Engraving on plexiglass, 60 x 80 cm, 25 unique prints, 2013 Printed at the Ateliers de Sèvres with the help of Olivier Moriette.
And twenty-one digital patterns (created from personal architecture drawings), 2013
    Other projects:
Exemplaires
The Belgian Cookbook
The Machine in the Ghost
Lato
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donne-moi tout ton argent</title>
      <link>http://carolinesorin.com/en/argent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:33:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://carolinesorin.com/en/argent/</guid>
      <description> Donne-moi tout ton argent A magazine made in collaboration with Andréa Corvo. A social approach of the French equivalent of the mall and its uses
21 x 29,7 cm, 50 pages, laser and silkscreen print, perfect binding, 2015
 Other projects:
Intra-muros
Confiture
Not in my Backyard
Top 10 Italia
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dérive</title>
      <link>http://carolinesorin.com/en/derive/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:33:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://carolinesorin.com/en/derive/</guid>
      <description>  Dérive I chose not to choose. A reflexive look on where I come from and why I’m here.
This book was made from personal archives (drawings and photographs) and failed silkscreen prints.
21 x 21 cm, 22 pages, laser and silkscreen print, perfect binding, 2015
 Other projects:
92 110
Image manquante
Long-Distance Memories
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Belgian Cookbook</title>
      <link>http://carolinesorin.com/en/belgian/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:32:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://carolinesorin.com/en/belgian/</guid>
      <description>The Belgian Cookbook Fifteen connected students working on the same Framapad, trying out print design with web tools.
Workshop under the direction of Stéphanie Vilayphiou and Colm O’Neill from OSP. Project made in collaboration with So-Hyun Bae.
10,5 x 14,8 cm, 300 index cards and a paper box, laser print, 2015
 About the workshop (articles in French):
http://osp.kitchen/workshop/strasbourg-html2print/
http://comgraph.hear.fr/2015/03/html-sauce-cocktail/
 Other projects:
Exemplaires
Lato
The Machine in the Ghost</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lato</title>
      <link>http://carolinesorin.com/en/lato/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:18:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://carolinesorin.com/en/lato/</guid>
      <description>Lato - A Small Open Source Dictionary Typographic specimen, poster and booklet at the same time. Presenting words of the open source world and their definitions, using the Lato free font.
20 posters-booklets of 29,7 x 42 cm (flat) and 10,5 x 14,8 cm when folded, laser print, 2016
    Other projects:
Exemplaires
The Belgian Cookbook
The Machine in the Ghost
Mash Up
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>92110</title>
      <link>http://carolinesorin.com/en/92110/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:31:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://carolinesorin.com/en/92110/</guid>
      <description>92 110 Coming back to a childhood city where I never really lived, looking for beauty and memories in the suburban landscape.
Digital photographies, 2015
    Other projects:
Image manquante
Long-Distance Memories
Dérive
     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Italia</title>
      <link>http://carolinesorin.com/en/italia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:31:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://carolinesorin.com/en/italia/</guid>
      <description>  Top 10 Italia A typographic specimen of the Italia font, using emblematic lyrics of famous Italian pop songs of the eighties to present the typeface. The size of the extracts depends on the selling numbers of the artist.
18 x 27 cm, laser print, saddle stitch binding, 2017
    Other projects:
Intra-muros
Confiture
Donne-moi tout ton argent
Not in my Backyard
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Machine in the Ghost</title>
      <link>http://carolinesorin.com/en/machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:31:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://carolinesorin.com/en/machine/</guid>
      <description>The Machine in the Ghost A book confronting the ghosts of the past with those of the present. Putting myself in the shoes of an early 20th century medium, I too, manipulate pictures to show the world the utlimate proof that spirits are all around us (and especially in our computers).
Book presented during the exhibition Haunted by Algorithms curated by Jeff Guess and Gwenola Wagon, at Galerie Ygrec](http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confiture</title>
      <link>http://carolinesorin.com/en/confiture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 17:26:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://carolinesorin.com/en/confiture/</guid>
      <description>Confiture Confiture (which means “jam” in French) is a project for a periodical publication focusing on social, cultural and visual studies. It aims at analysing popular cultural practices in the present world and societies. Each issue is dedicated to a different question such as cultural legitimacy, digital communities or matters of representation in pop culture. The title refers to a French idiomatic expression basically saying that the less one knows, the more one brags about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image manquante</title>
      <link>http://carolinesorin.com/en/manquant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 18:35:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://carolinesorin.com/en/manquant/</guid>
      <description>Image manquante Going through my archives, I selected the negatives of photographs that didn’t come out. Labelled as failed by the photo laboratory, they were not printed. By scanning and enlarging them, I gave them an existence.
Project made during a workshop with David De Beyter
21 x 29,7, 4 booklets of 16 images, laser printed, 2017
   Other projects:
92 110
Long-Distance Memories
Dérive
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long-Distance Memories</title>
      <link>http://carolinesorin.com/en/longdistance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:30:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://carolinesorin.com/en/longdistance/</guid>
      <description>  Long-Distance Memories I go for a virtual journey through memories, pictures and Google Street View, to places where I have lived. Secretly hoping to find traces of what I left of me there.
Photographs, video (13min), sound, 2017
  Other projects:
92 110
Image manquante
Dérive
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exemplaires</title>
      <link>http://carolinesorin.com/en/exemplaires/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 18:34:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://carolinesorin.com/en/exemplaires/</guid>
      <description>Imprimer l&amp;rsquo;exposition Catalogue produced for the 2017 biennal &amp;ldquo;Exemplaires, formes et pratiques de l’édition” (Exemplars, forms and practices in publishing). It presents the book selection of the Hear (on the topic of the exhibition catalogue). Analytical texts and pictures presenting the books go with three interviews with artists and graphic designers. This project is a teamwork where we all both created the content (words and pictures) and designed the form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intra-muros</title>
      <link>http://carolinesorin.com/en/intramuros/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 18:11:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://carolinesorin.com/en/intramuros/</guid>
      <description> Other projects:
Confiture
Donne-moi tout ton argent
Not in my Backyard
Top 10 Italia
 Intra-muros Where does Paris begins? Is the official border the only evidence of passing from one city another? Standing on this invisible line, I photographed each side of the city on the spot where it changes its name.
21 x 29,7 cm, 40 pages, laser print, saddle stitch binding, 2017
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>http://carolinesorin.com/en/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:31:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://carolinesorin.com/en/home/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>