<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Caroline Sorin</title>
    <link>https://carolinesorin.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Caroline Sorin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:33:56 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://carolinesorin.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Not in my Backyard</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/en/backyard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:32:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/en/backyard/</guid>
      <description>Not in my Backyard In 2013, an abandoned train station in a wealthy neighborhood of Paris is about to be replaced by a block of council flats despite the loud opposition of its neighbors. A few weeks before the works begin, I went there to immortalize this urban wasteland, symbol of the class war in the 16th arrondissement.
20 x 28 cm, 16 pages, digital print, saddle stitch binding, 2013</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not in my Backyard</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/backyard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:32:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/backyard/</guid>
      <description>Not in my Backyard En 2013, le site de l&amp;rsquo;ancienne gare d&amp;rsquo;Auteuil, à l&amp;rsquo;abandon depuis plusieurs dizaines d&amp;rsquo;années, est sur le point de laisser la place à un projet immobilier HLM malgré l&amp;rsquo;opposition des riverains qui déposent des recours depuis 2009. Quelques mois avant le début des travaux, j&amp;rsquo;ai immortalisé ce bout de friche, objet de discorde et symbole de la lutte des classes dans le seizième arrondissement.
20 x 28 cm, 16 pages, impression numérique, piqûre à cheval, 2013</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mash Up</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/en/archi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/en/archi/</guid>
      <description> Mash Up Engraving on plexiglass, 60 x 80 cm, 25 unique prints, 2013. Printed at the Ateliers de Sèvres with the help of Olivier Moriette.
And twenty-one digital patterns (created from personal architecture drawings), 2013
    Other projects:
Exemplaires
The Belgian Cookbook
The Machine in the Ghost
Lato
Dérive
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mash Up</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/archi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/archi/</guid>
      <description> Mash Up Pointe sèche sur plexiglas, 60 x 80 cm,
vingt-cinq tirages uniques, 2013
Imprimé aux Ateliers de Sèvres avec l’aide d’Olivier Moriette
Et vingt-et-un motifs numériques (créés à partir de dessins d&amp;rsquo;architecture personnels), 2013
    Autres projets :
Exemplaires
The Belgian Cookbook
The Machine in the Ghost
Lato
Dérive
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donne-moi tout ton argent</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/en/argent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:33:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/en/argent/</guid>
      <description> Donne-moi tout ton argent (Give me all your money)
A magazine made with Andréa Corvo. An analytical approach of a French mall and its uses.
21 x 29,7 cm, 50 pages, laser and silkscreen print, perfect binding, 2015
 Other projects:
Intra-muros
Confiture
Not in my Backyard
Exemplaires
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donne-moi tout ton argent</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/argent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:33:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/argent/</guid>
      <description> Donne-moi tout ton argent Magazine réalisé à quatre mains avec Andréa Corvo. Une enquête anthropologique au centre commercial.
21 x 29,7 cm, 50 pages, impression laser et sérigraphie, dos carré-collé, dix exemplaires, 2015
Textes et mise en page : Andréa Corvo &amp;amp; Caroline Sorin
Dessins : Caroline Sorin
Photographies : Andréa Corvo
Suivi : Jérôme Saint-Loubert Bié
 Autres projets :
Intra-muros
Confiture
Not in my Backyard
Exemplaires
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dérive</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/en/derive/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:33:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/en/derive/</guid>
      <description>  Dérive I chose not to choose. A reflexive look on where I come from and why I’m here.
This book was made from personal archives (drawings and photographs) and failed silkscreen prints.
21 x 21 cm, 22 pages, laser and silkscreen print, perfect binding, 2015
 Other projects:
92 110
Image manquante
Long-Distance Memories
Exemplaires
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dérive</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/derive/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:33:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/derive/</guid>
      <description>  Dérive Choisir de ne pas choisir. Une réflexion sur d’où je viens et pourquoi je suis là. Regarder le chemin parcouru pour mieux voir où l&amp;rsquo;on va.
Édition faite à partir d&amp;rsquo;archives personnelles (photographies et dessins) et de tirages sérigraphiques ratés.
21 x 21 cm, 22 pages, impression laser et sérigraphie, dos carré-collé, 2015
 Autres projets :
92 110
Image manquante
Long-Distance Memories
Exemplaires
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Belgian Cookbook</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/en/belgian/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:32:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/en/belgian/</guid>
      <description>The Belgian Cookbook Fifteen connected students worked on the same Framapad, trying out print design with web tools.
Workshop under the direction of Stéphanie Vilayphiou and Colm O&amp;rsquo;Neill from OSP. Project made with So-Hyun Bae.
10,5 x 14,8 cm, 300 index cards and a paper box, laser print, 2015
 About the workshop (articles in French):
http://osp.kitchen/workshop/strasbourg-html2print/
http://comgraph.hear.fr/2015/03/html-sauce-cocktail/
 Other projects:
Exemplaires
Lato
The Machine in the Ghost
Mash Up</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Belgian Cookbook</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/belgian/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:32:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/belgian/</guid>
      <description>The Belgian Cookbook À partir d’un texte donné et sur le même Framapad, quinze étudiants connectés expérimentent la mise en page papier avec les outils du web.
Workshop dirigé par Stéphanie Vilayphiou et Colm O&amp;rsquo;Neill de OSP. Projet réalisé avec So-Hyun Bae.
10,5 x 14,8 cm, 300 cartes et une boîte en papier, 2015
 À propos du workshop :
http://osp.kitchen/workshop/strasbourg-html2print/
http://comgraph.hear.fr/2015/03/html-sauce-cocktail/
 Autres projets :
Exemplaires
Lato
The Machine in the Ghost</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lato</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/en/lato/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:18:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/en/lato/</guid>
      <description>Lato - A Small Open Source Dictionary Typographic specimen, poster and booklet at the same time. Presenting words of the open source world and their definitions, using the Lato free font.
20 posters-booklets of 29,7 x 42 cm (flat) and 10,5 x 14,8 cm when folded, laser print, 2016
  Other projects:
Exemplaires
The Belgian Cookbook
The Machine in the Ghost
Mash Up
Long-Distance Memories
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lato</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/lato/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:18:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/lato/</guid>
      <description>Lato - Petit dictionnaire de l&amp;rsquo;open source Spécimen typographique bilingue pour la typographie libre Lato. À la fois poster recto verso et livret présentant une sélection de mots clés de l&amp;rsquo;open source et leur définition.
20 livrets-posters, 29,7 x 42 cm à plat et 10,5 x 14,8 cm plié, impression laser, 2016
Suivi : Yohanna-My Nguyen
  Autres projets :
Exemplaires
The Belgian Cookbook
The Machine in the Ghost</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Machine in the Ghost</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/en/machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:31:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/en/machine/</guid>
      <description>The Machine in the Ghost A book confronting ghosts of the past with those of the present. Putting myself in the shoes of an early 20th century medium, I too, manipulate pictures to show the world the utlimate proof that spirits are all around us (and especially in our computers).
Book presented during the exhibition Haunted by Algorithms curated by Jeff Guess and Gwenola Wagon, at Galerie Ygrec](http://www.ensapc.fr/fr/ygrec/galerie), Paris (21 january to 5 march 2017).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Machine in the Ghost</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:31:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/machine/</guid>
      <description>The Machine in the Ghost Confronter les fantômes et les regards à un siècle de distance. Manipuler les images, à la manière d’un médium du XIXe siècle, en laissant l’ordinateur révéler la présence d’esprits et créer de nouveaux fantômes faits de données détériorées.
Livre présenté dans le cadre de l’exposition Haunted by Algorithms créée par Jeff Guess et Gwenola Wagon à la Galerie Ygrec, Paris (du 21 janvier au 5 mars 2017).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>92110</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/en/92110/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:31:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/en/92110/</guid>
      <description>92 110 Coming back to a childhood city where I never really lived, looking for beauty and memories in the suburban landscape.
Digital photographies, 2015
    Other projects:
Image manquante
Long-Distance Memories
Dérive
Intra-muros
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>92110</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/92110/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:31:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/92110/</guid>
      <description>92 110 Reportage photographique à Clichy-la-Garenne, ville d’enfance longtemps détestée, aujourd’hui désertée. Quand il ne reste que le soleil sur le bitume et le souvenir des rires entre les voitures.
photographies numériques, 2015 - 2017
    Autres projets:
Image manquante
Long-Distance Memories
Dérive
Intra-muros
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confiture</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/en/confiture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 17:26:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/en/confiture/</guid>
      <description>Confiture Confiture (“jam”) is a project for a periodical publication focusing on social, cultural and visual studies. It aims at analysing popular cultural practices in the present world and societies. Each issue is dedicated to a different question such as cultural legitimacy, digital communities or matters of representation in pop culture. The title refers to a French idiomatic expression basically saying that the less one knows, the more one brags about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confiture</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/confiture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 17:26:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/confiture/</guid>
      <description>Confiture Confiture est un projet de revue de sociologie culturelle.
Au croisement des visual et cultural studies, elle se propose d’analyser la culture et en particulier les cultures populaires ou marginales. Le numéro zéro porte sur les questions de légitimité culturelle.
13,5 x 25,5 cm, impression numérique laser, dos carré-collé, 2017
Suivi : Philippe Delangle
 Autres projets :
Intra-muros
Donne-moi tout ton argent
Not in my Backyard
Dérive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image manquante</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/en/manquant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 18:35:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/en/manquant/</guid>
      <description>Image manquante Going through my archives, I selected the negatives of photographs that didn’t come out. Labelled as failed by the photo laboratory, they were not printed. By scanning and enlarging them, I gave them a chance to become something else.
Project made during a workshop with David De Beyter
21 x 29,7, 4 booklets of 16 images, laser printed, 2017
   Other projects:
92 110
Long-Distance Memories</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image manquante</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/manquant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 18:35:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/manquant/</guid>
      <description>Image manquante Fouillant parmi mes archives, j’ai sélectionné les négatifs de photos jugées ratées par le laboratoire qui les a développées et pour lesquelles je n’ai donc aucun tirage. En les scannant et agrandissant, j’ai découvert et redonné vie à ces images non-conformes.
Projet réalisé dans le cadre d&amp;rsquo;un workshop avec David De Beyter
21 x 29,7 cm, 4 livrets de 16 images, impression numérique laser, 2017
   Autres projets :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long-Distance Memories</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/en/longdistance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:30:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/en/longdistance/</guid>
      <description>  Long-Distance Memories I went on a virtual journey through memories, pictures and Google Street View, to places where I have lived. Secretly hoping to find traces of what I left of me there.
Photographs, video (13min), sound, 2017
   Other projects:
92 110
Image manquante
Dérive
The Machine in the Ghost
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long-Distance Memories</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/longdistance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:30:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/longdistance/</guid>
      <description>  Long-Distance Memories J’embarque pour un voyage virtuel à travers photos d&amp;rsquo;enfance, souvenirs et Google Street View vers les endroits où j’ai vécu, espérant y retrouver des traces de mon passage.
Dimensions variables, photos, vidéo (13min), son, 2017
Suivi : Laura Henno
   Autres projets :
92 110
Image manquante
Dérive
The Machine in the Ghost
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exemplaires</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/en/exemplaires/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 18:34:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/en/exemplaires/</guid>
      <description>Imprimer l&amp;rsquo;exposition Catalogue produced for the 2017 biennal &amp;ldquo;Exemplaires, formes et pratiques de l’édition&amp;rdquo; (Exemplars, forms and practices in publishing). It presents the HEAR&amp;rsquo;s book selection (on the topic of exhibition catalogues). Analytical texts and reproductions of the books are accompanied by three interviews with artists and graphic designers. This project is a teamwork where we all four created the content (words and pictures) and designed the form.
Part of the exhibition &amp;ldquo;Exemplaires, formes et pratiques de l’édition&amp;rdquo; curated by HEAR students, at La Chaufferie, Strasbourg (30 March to 30 April 2017).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exemplaires</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/exemplaires/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 18:34:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/exemplaires/</guid>
      <description>Imprimer l&amp;rsquo;exposition Catalogue réalisé pour la deuxième édition de la biennale &amp;ldquo;Exemplaires, formes et pratiques de l’édition&amp;rdquo;, présentant la sélection d&amp;rsquo;ouvrages de la HEAR (sur le thème du catalogue d&amp;rsquo;exposition). Les textes d&amp;rsquo;analyse et photographies des objets retenus sont accompagnés de trois entretiens avec des artistes et graphistes à l&amp;rsquo;origine de certains des ouvrages présentés. Ce projet est un travail d’équipe pour lequel nous avons toutes créé la forme et le contenu (textes et images).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intra-muros</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/en/intramuros/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 18:11:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/en/intramuros/</guid>
      <description> Other projects:
Confiture
Donne-moi tout ton argent
Not in my Backyard
Mash Up
 Intra-muros Where does Paris begin? Is the official border the only evidence of passing from one city another? Standing on this invisible line, I photographed each side of the city where it changes its name.
21 x 29,7 cm, 40 pages, laser print, saddle stitch binding, 2017
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intra-muros</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/intramuros/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 18:11:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/intramuros/</guid>
      <description>Autres projets :
Confiture
Donne-moi tout ton argent
Not in my Backyard
Mash Up
 Intra-muros Où finit Paris ? Où commence la banlieue ? La frontière administrative est-elle la seule trace du passage d’une ville à l’autre ? Depuis cette ligne invisible, j’ai photographié chaque côté de la ville à l’endroit où elle change de nom.
21 x 29,7 cm, 40 pages, impression numérique laser, piqûre à cheval, 2017</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is this you in the video?</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/en/aram/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/en/aram/</guid>
      <description>Is this you in the video? Communication for Aram Bartholl&amp;rsquo;s exhibition at La Chaufferie, Strasbourg.
Poster 60 x 80 cm, invitation 29,7 x 42 cm (flat), digital communication, 2018
        Other projects:
Exemplaires
Lato
The Machine in the Ghost
Mash Up
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is this you in the video?</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/aram/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/aram/</guid>
      <description>Is this you in the video? Communication pour l’exposition d’Aram Bartholl à La Chaufferie, Strasbourg.
Affiche 60 x 80 cm, invitation 29,7 x 42 cm (dépliée), bannières numériques, 2018
Suivi : Jérôme Saint-Loubert Bié
        Autres projets :
Exemplaires
Lato
The Machine in the Ghost
Mash Up
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ailleurs</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/ailleurs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/ailleurs/</guid>
      <description>Ailleurs Rapport d&amp;rsquo;échange et rapport de stage documentant de façon plus ou moins précise mes aventures européennes.
 Rotterdam : 12 x 15 cm, 42 pages, impression numérique laser, reliure spirale, 2018
 Munich : 9,5 x 21 cm, 20 pages, impression numérique laser, 2018
   Autres projets :
The Belgian Cookbook
Image manquante
Long-Distance Memories
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elsewhere</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/en/ailleurs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/en/ailleurs/</guid>
      <description>Elsewhere Internship and exchange reports loosely documenting my European adventures.
 Rotterdam: 12 x 15 cm, 42 pages, digital printing, wire o binding, 2018
 Munich: 9,5 x 21 cm, 20 pages, digital printing, 2018
   Other projects:
The Belgian Cookbook
Image manquante
Long-Distance Memories
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crossing</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/en/crossing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/en/crossing/</guid>
      <description>Crossing Graphic design for the second issue of Volkswagen Group Culture magazine.
Writing: Nansen &amp;amp; Piccard
Artistic direction: Alexis Zurflüh and Ludwig Haslberger
21,5 x 28 cm, 64 pages, offset printing, Swiss binding, 2018
    Other projects:
Elsewhere
Lato
The Machine in the Ghost
Is this you in the video?
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crossing</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/crossing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/fr/crossing/</guid>
      <description>Crossing Design graphique pour le deuxième numéro du magazine culturel édité par Volkswagen.
Rédaction : Nansen &amp;amp; Piccard
Direction artistique : Alexis Zurflüh et Ludwig Haslberger
21,5 x 28 cm, 64 pages, impression offset, reliure suisse, 2018
    Autres projets :
Ailleurs
Lato
The Machine in the Ghost
Is this you in the video?
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/en/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:31:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/en/home/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/about/about_en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 19:10:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/about/about_en/</guid>
      <description>Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Graphic Design
HEAR (Haute École des Arts du Rhin), Strasbourg
June 2019
Exchange semester, Graphic Design department
Willem de Kooning Academy, Rotterdam
August 2017 - February 2018
Bachelor in Graphic Design
HEAR, Strasbourg
June 2017
 Internship ⇾ (Team) Alexis Zurflüh, Munich
Editorial design and video making
July - September 2018
Visual communication for Is this you in the video?
and Morituri te salutant ! Posters, flyers and digital communication</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>À propos</title>
      <link>https://carolinesorin.com/about/about_fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 19:10:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carolinesorin.com/about/about_fr/</guid>
      <description>DNSEP Communication graphique (félicitations)
HEAR (Haute école des arts du Rhin), Strasbourg
juin 2019
Semestre d’échange, section Graphic Design
Willem de Kooning Academy, Rotterdam
août 2017 - février 2018
DNAP Communication graphique (mention)
HEAR (Haute école des arts du Rhin), Strasbourg
juin 2017
 Stage ⇾ (Team) Alexis Zurflüh, Munich
Design éditorial et vidéo
juillet - septembre 2018
Communication graphique pour les expositions
Is this you in the video? et Morituri te salutant !</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
